OH... UH, HEY, RACH.
UH, I WAS
JUST COMING OVER HERE TO, UH...
OH, WAIT.
I DON'T HAVE TO LIE TO YOU.
YOU DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
UH... I'M EATING THEIR FOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ROSS IS ON A DATE
WITH MY SISTER
AND THEY SHUT THE DRAPES
TWO-AND-A-HALF HOURS AGO.
WHOA. I DIDN'T KNOW
WE COULD DATE YOUR SISTER.
JOEY, WE KNOW YOU
STEAL OUR FOOD.
I'M GOOD.
OH, ARE THE
DRAPES STILL
CLOSED, HONEY?
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHO SHOULD HAVE
SHUT THEIR DRAPES
IS THAT PERVERTED OLD COUPLE
TWO DOORS OVER.
IS THAT A SWING?
OH, DON'T EVEN ASK.
YECCH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE ROSS
IS GOING OUT
WITH RACHEL'S SISTER.
WHEN CHANDLER MADE OUT
WITH MY SISTER
I WAS MAD AT HIM
FOR TEN YEARS.
THAT WAS, LIKE,
FIVE YEARS AGO.
YEAH, YOU GOT FIVE YEARS LEFT.
JOEY...
YOU WANT TO MAKE IT SIX?!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OH, ROSS! HEY!
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
THERE YOU ARE.
HEY.
GIVE ME A CUP
OF COFFEE.
SO HOW WAS YOUR
BIG DATE LAST NIGHT?
UH, IT WAS OKAY.
IT WAS FUN.
YEAH? IT WAS FUN?
MMM.
GREAT.
SO, UH...
SO, DID YOU GUYS
HIT IT OFF?
I GUESS SO.
SO, D-DID
ANYTHING HAPPEN?
BECAUSE RUMOR HAS IT
YOU GUYS SHUT THE DRAPES.
NO, NO.
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I SHUT THE DRAPES
TO SHOW HER SLIDES
OF MY FAVORITE FOSSILS.
OH, SLIDES!
( chuckling):
SO REALLY NOTHING HAPPENED.
WELL... SOMETHING COULD HAVE
HAPPENED, ALL RIGHT?
SHE REALLY DUG MY SLIDES
AND SHE WAS DEFINITELY
GIVING ME THE VIBE.
WAS IT THE "PLEASE DON'T SHOW ME
ANOTHER PICTURE
OF A TRILOBITE" VIBE?
ANYWAY...
IF SHE WASN'T INTO ME
WHY-WHY WOULD SHE
ASK ME OUT AGAIN?
SHE ASKED YOU OUT AGAIN?
YEAH. UH-HUH.
TOMORROW NIGHT.
MMM.
VALENTINE'S DAY.
THE MOST ROMANTIC
DAY OF THE YEAR.
WHO KNOWS WHAT COULD HAPPEN.
I MIGHT NOT BE SHUTTING
MY DRAPES TO SHOW HER MY SLIDES,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
I CAN'T, I CAN'T, I CAN'T--
I'M NOT GOOD WITH THE
YOU-AND-MY-SISTER THING, OKAY?
I JUST CAN'T.
IT'S JUST TOO WEIRD,
ALL RIGHT?
I IMAGINE THE TWO
OF YOU TOGETHER.
I JUST FREAK OUT!
OKAY...
IT FREAKS ME OUT
AND I CAN'T DO IT.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
HEY, IT'S TOO WEIRD
FOR YOU.
I WON'T SEE HER AGAIN.
THANK YOU. I... YEAH.
I MEAN, AFTER TOMORROW NIGHT.
NO-NO-NO! NO-NO-NO!
PLEASE, ROSS, I CAN'T,
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT'S GOING TO FREAK
ME OUT!
OKAY, OKAY... OKAY.
I'LL TELL HER TONIGHT
I CAN'T SEE HER ANYMORE.
( sobbing ):
OH, THANKS.
YOU WANT ME TO CALL HER
RIGHT NOW?
OH, NO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO. I MEAN, COME ON.
THAT'S CRAZ...
I MEAN, THAT'S CRAZY.
UH-HUH.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH YOU?
WHAT IS GOING ON
WELL, UM...
OH! I MAY BE TEACHING
ANOTHER CLASS THIS SEMESTER.
YEAH, DO IT NOW.
CALL HER RIGHT NOW.
( sobbing ):
THIS IS MY FAVORITE PART.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
SADDER THAN THIS? BAMBI.
I CRIED FOR THREE DAYS
WITH THAT MOVIE.
NO, WAIT-- TWO.
'CAUSE ON THE THIRD DAY,
MY MOTHER KILLED HERSELF
SO I WAS PARTLY
CRYING FOR THAT.
WELL, SEE, NOW, THAT,
I CAN SEE CRYING OVER,
BUT BAMBI IS A CARTOON.
YOU DIDN'T CRY
WHEN BAMBI'S MOTHER DIED?
YES, IT WAS VERY SAD
WHEN THE GUY STOPPED
DRAWING THE DEER.
CHANDLER, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH CRYING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SO MACHO ALL THE TIME.
I'M NOT MACHO.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS THINKING.
NO, I GUESS I JUST NEVER
REALLY CRIED, YOU KNOW?
I'M NOT A CRYING
KIND OF GUY.
COME ON, MAN,
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
THAT GETS YOU CHOKED UP.
LIKE, UH...
UH, WHAT IF YOU SAW
A THREE-LEGGED PUPPY.
I'D BE SAD, SURE...
BUT I WOULDN'T CRY.
OKAY, WHAT IF THE PUPPY
SAID, "HELP ME, CHANDLER.
ALL THE OTHER PUPPIES
PICK ON ME."
CRY? I JUST FOUND
A TALKING PUPPY.
I'M RICH.
OH... I'VE GOT IT.
I HAVE GOT IT.
PICTURES FROM
YOUR CHILDHOOD.
THIS'LL GET YOU
GOING GOOD. OKAY...
ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S
GOING ON THERE?
AH, THAT'S PARENTS DAY,
FIRST GRADE.
THAT'S ME WITH
THE JANITOR, MARTIN.
WHERE ARE YOUR PARENTS?
OH, THEY DIDN'T
WANT TO COME.
OH, CHANDLER.
POOR THING.
SO, THAT STORY
DOESN'T MAKE YOU CRY?
NO! LOOK, I DON'T CRY.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL,
OKAY?
NO, IT'S NOT OKAY!
( voice cracking ):
IT'S NOT OKAY AT ALL.
YOU'RE DEAD INSIDE!
EXCUSE ME.
YEAH?
ARE YOU PHOEBE BUFFAY?
YEAH.
( gasps )
CAN I GET YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
I'M YOUR BIGGEST FAN.
OH, YOU'RE MY BIGGEST FAN?
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO MEET YOU. HI.
SURE. YEAH.
WOW.
WOW, THANKS A LOT.
I JUST WANT TO SAY
I THINK YOU'RE
REALLY TALENTED.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT
'CAUSE YOU'RE
MY BIGGEST FAN.
JOEY, LISTEN
TAKE GOOD CARE
OF THAT GUY, OKAY?
HE'S A FAN.
OH.
BYE.
SO...
YOU SAW ME
ON DAYS OF OUR LIVES, HUH?
WANT ME TO DO A LITTLE
DR. DRAKE RAMORAY FOR YOU?
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
BUT I JUST GOT
PHOEBE BUFFAY'S AUTOGRAPH.
OH. YOUR PHOEBE'S FAN.
OH, YEAH.
I'VE SEEN ALL HER MOVIES.
MOVIES?
THAT WAS PHOEBE BUFFAY,
THE PORN STAR.
( chuckles )
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO, NO, IT WAS.
SHE WAS IN
SEX TOY STORY II.
LAWRENCE OF ALABIA.
AND I GOT
HER AUTOGRAPH.
THE GUYS
AT THE COMIC BOOK STORE
AREN'T GOING
TO BELIEVE THIS.
GUNTHER.
HEY, DON'T LET THAT GUY
IN HERE ANYMORE.
HE JUST SAID PHOEBE'S
A PORN STAR.
WELL, I WOULDN'T
CALL HER A STAR
BUT SHE'S REALLY GOOD.
YOU SHOULD CHECK OUT
INSPECT HER GADGET.
HEY.
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE
WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
ROSS JUST TOTALLY
BLEW ME OFF
AND HE DIDN'T EVEN
TELL ME WHY.
AH, WELL.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY?
THE BEST THING TO DO
TO GET OVER A GUY
IS TO START DATING
SOMEONE ELSE.
OH! OH, THERE IS
THIS GREAT GUY
YOU WILL JUST LOVE
AT WORK NAMED BOB.
HE'S A REAL UP-AND-COMER
IN HUMAN RESOURCES.
YOU KNOW, THANKS FOR
TRYING TO CHEER ME UP
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO DATE
SOME RANDOM GUY
FROM YOUR WORK.
NOT RANDOM. BOB.
OH... IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE
I'M NOT MATURE ENOUGH
OR SMART ENOUGH, OR...
MAYBE HE DOESN'T LIKE
THE WAY I DRESS.
NO, THAT CAN'T BE IT.
IT'S REALLY GOT TO BE
THE SMART THING.
OH, I'M
SO STUPID.
I'M JUST THIS, LIKE,
INCREDIBLY PRETTY, STUPID GIRL.
NO, HONEY...
OKAY. OKAY.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY ROSS CANCELED
THE DATE?
BECAUSE I ASKED HIM TO.
YOU ASKED HIM TO?
MM-HMM.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU ARE MY SISTER
AND ROSS AND I HAVE
THIS HUGE HISTORY...
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU WANT TO GO OUT WITH ROSS?
NO.
YOU DON'T WANT HIM, BUT YOU
DON'T WANT ME TO HAVE HIM?
YOU KNOW BOB
IN HUMAN RESOURCES?
OH! I CANNOT BELIEVE
YOU DID THIS TO ME!
YOU HAD ME DOUBTING
HOW SMART I WAS...
( gasps )
YOU HAD ME DOUBTING
MY FASHION SENSE.
COME ON! THIS IS NOT
THAT BIG A DEAL.
YOU JUST DON'T DATE ROSS.
THERE'S A MILLION
OTHER GUYS OUT THERE.
HEY-- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU
WHAT TO DO.
I AM TELLING YOU
WHAT NOT TO DO.
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS
SO JEALOUS OF ME?
OH, JILL, THIS IS NOT ABOUT
ME BEING JEALOUS OF YOU.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU
BEING A BRAT--
WANTING WHAT YOU CAN'T HAVE.
"CAN'T HAVE"?
EXCUSE ME. THE ONLY THING
I CAN'T HAVE IS DAIRY!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU JUST BLEW
YOUR CHANCES AT DATING BOB.
WHO?
( screaming ):
IN HUMAN RESOURCES!
I AM JEALOUS OF HER?!
I MEAN, WHO DOES SHE THINK
SHE IS, PRINCESS CAROLINE?
YOU'RE JEALOUS
OF PRINCESS CAROLINE?
DO I HAVE MY OWN CASTLE?
HEY, UH,
PHOEBE'S NOT HERE, IS SHE?
NO.
OH, GREAT. DID YOU
GET A MOVIE?
UH... YEAH, YEAH.
BUT, UH... I DON'T THINK
IT'S THE KIND
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE.
YOU DIDN'T GET
MORE MOVIES
THAT ARE GOING TO HAVE US
REACHING FOR THE TISSUES
ALL NIGHT, DID YOU?
SORT OF.
GUYS, WHAT'S GOING ON?
UH...
PHOEBE'S A PORN STAR!
WHAT?
Ross:
YEAH!
COME HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
"PHOEBE BUFFAY IN
BUFFAY THE VAMPIRE LAYER."
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S PHOEBE.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
WELL, DOWN AT THE ADULT
VIDEO PLACE ON BLEEKER.
AND I SAW JOEY
WAS ABOUT TO GO IN
SO I RAN IN AHEAD OF HIM
TO-TO SURPRISE HIM
AND... AND THEN...
( forced laugh )
THEN I PRETENDED
THAT I DIDN'T KNOW
HE WAS IN THERE.
WOW. I MEAN, I JUST...
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
YOU THINK YOU KNOW SOMEONE...
EVEN PHOEBE, WHO'S ALWAYS BEEN
SOMEWHAT OF A QUESTION MARK.
MMM.
THIS IS SO BIZARRE.
I GUESS IT KIND OF
MAKES SENSE, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, SHE HAD
SUCH A TERRIBLE CHILDHOOD.
I HAD A TERRIBLE CHILDHOOD
AND I DON'T DO PORN.
YES, BUT YOU'RE DEAD INSIDE.
OH. YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I BETTER TAKE THAT BACK.
WH-WHY?
WE CAN'T WATCH THAT.
I MEAN, THAT'S PHOEBE.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE CAN'T.
WE SHOULDN'T WATCH THIS.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
THAT GOES BACK.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
A LITTLE BIT.
HOW ABOUT
JUST THE FIRST HALF?
NO... HEY, NO,
THIS IS WRONG, YOU GUYS!
PHOEBE'S OUR FRIEND.
I'M NOT GOING TO WATCH IT.
YEAH!
GOOD FOR YOU, JOE.
Ah, I thought
I'd find you here...
Nosferatool.
Buffay, are you going to plunge
your stake into my dark places?
Actually, I was kind of hoping
it would be
the other way around.
Monica:
HOLD ON A SECOND.
WHAT IS THAT
ON HER ANKLE?
HER ANKLE
IS WHAT YOU'RE WATCHING?
WELL, IT'S HARD TO TELL...
OH, GOD, IF SHE WOULD JUST
STOP MOVING.
SHE'S JUST DOING
HER JOB.
YOU SICK BASTARDS.
OH, IT'S A TATTOO.
THAT'S WEIRD.
PHOEBE DOESN'T...
WAIT, THAT'S URSULA!
THAT'S NOT PHOEBE.
THAT IS URSULA!
WAIT! WAIT!
THEN I CAN WATCH THAT.
REWIND IT, REWIND IT.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT AM I DOING?!
HEY, SWEETIE.
HEY.
CHICKEN SOUP FOR THE SOUL?
THERE'S NO BACK TO THIS COUCH.
WHY ARE YOU READING THIS?
YOU HATE THIS KIND OF STUFF.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT I FIGURED
I'D GIVE IT A SHOT.
MAYBE ONE OF THOSE STORIES
WILL MAKE ME CRY
AND THEN YOU WOULDN'T THINK
I WAS
YOU KNOW, ALL DEAD INSIDE.
AH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
BUT, CHANDLER, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU CAN'T CRY.
I LOVE YOU.
AH, THAT MAKES ME FEEL SO WARM
IN MY HOLLOW TIN CHEST.
STOP IT.
NO, I MEAN, COME ON,
SERIOUSLY, THINK ABOUT IT.
WE GET MARRIED--
I'M UP AT THE ALTAR,
AND I'M LIKE THIS...
I WON'T CARE...
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT
YOU'LL BE FEELING IT
ALL IN HERE.
YEAH?
YEAH.
AND IF WE HAVE
A BABY ONE DAY
AND THE DOCTOR
HANDS IT TO YOU
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM
AND YOU DON'T CRY...
SO WHAT?
AND IF WE TAKE HIM TO COLLEGE
AND WE COME HOME
AND WE SEE HIS EMPTY
ROOM FOR THE FIRST TIME
AND YOU GOT NOTHING...
WON'T MATTER TO ME.
OKAY.
WELL, I WON'T WORRY
ABOUT THIS ANYMORE THEN.
YEAH, AND IF I DIE...
FROM A LONG ILLNESS
AND YOU'RE WRITING
OUT MY EULOGY
AND YOU OPEN THE DESK DRAWER
AND YOU FIND A NOTE FROM ME
THAT SAYS, "I WILL
ALWAYS BE WITH YOU"
AND YOU STILL CAN'T
SHED ONE TINY TEAR...
I KNOW YOU'LL BE
CRYING A RIVER INSIDE.
OH, I LOVE YOU SO...
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?!
WHAT?
YOU CAN'T SHED A TEAR
FOR YOUR DEAD WIFE?!
NOW, I LEFT YOU A NOTE
FROM THE BEYOND.
SO YOU DIDN'T MEAN
ANY OF THAT?
NO, YOU ROBOT!
( doorbell ringing )
YOU DAMN KIDS.
YOU RING MY BELL
ONE MORE TIME, I SWEAR TO...
OH, JILL.
UM, THAT'S JUST
A LITTLE GAME
I PLAY WITH THE KIDS
DOWN THE HALL.
UM...
THEY'VE REALLY TAKEN
A LIKING TO ME.
UH, WHAT-WHAT-WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
RACHEL AND I HAD
A REALLY BIG FIGHT.
CAN I COME IN?
I KNOW WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO SEE EACH OTHER ANY MORE,
AND I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
IT'S JUST THAT I DON'T
KNOW ANYBODY IN THE CITY
AND I REALLY NEED SOMEBODY
TO TALK TO ABOUT IT.
OF COURSE. WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
OKAY, UM...
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT MIGHT
REALLY CHEER ME UP?
WHAT?
SEEING SOME MORE
OF YOUR SUPER COOL SLIDES.
WOW, REALLY?
TOTALLY. I LOVED THEM
AND MAYBE YOU COULD FINISH
TELLING ME
ABOUT ALL THE DIFFERENT KINDS
OF SAND.
WELL, I'D LOVE TO.
YOU WAIT RIGHT HERE.
I'LL GO GET THE PROJECTOR
AND MY NOTES.
OH, GREAT. THANKS, ROSS.
YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD FRIEND.
HEY, HAVE YOU GUYS SEEN JILL?
I CAN'T FIND HER ANYWHERE.
NO, I HAVEN'T.
WELL, IS ROSS HOME?
MAYBE I'LL CALL HIM
AND SEE IF HE'S SEEN...
( gasps )
Ursula:
WHO IS IT?
IT'S PHOEBE...
PHOEBE.
HEY.
OH, GOD.
SO-SO YOU'RE MAKING
PORN MOVIES.
NO, I'M NOT.
Man:
WE'RE STILL ROLLING.
YOU'RE MAKING ONE
RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GO, PHOEBE.
AND YOU'RE USING MY NAME.
YEAH, CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING?
PHOEBE, COME ON.
LOOK, I'M TALKING
RIGHT NOW.
YOU MEAN HER.
YOU KNOW...
TWIN STUFF IS ALWAYS
A REAL BIG SELLER.
WHAT?
YEAH, I COULD TALK THEM
INTO GIVING YOU LIKE...
$30.
NO. NO WAY. NO.
AND STOP USING MY NAME.
AND SHAME ON YOU
AND SHAME ON ALL OF YOU.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING...
ESPECIALLY YOU WITH... THAT.
SLIDES ARE ALMOST READY.
YEAH.
OOH, I KNOW WHAT
THIS IS MISSING.
ALCOHOL.
UH, OKAY, WELL, THERE'S WINE
IN THE KITCHEN.
OH, GREAT.
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
WHAT IS MY SISTER DOING THERE,
AND WHY ARE THE DRAPES SHUT?
OKAY, RACH, CALM DOWN, OKAY?
SHE'S... SHE'S REALLY UPSET.
WE'RE JUST TALKING.
I THINK SHE'S TRYING TO MAKE
SOMETHING HAPPEN WITH YOU
TO GET BACK AT ME.
OH, SO THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
SHE COULD BE HERE, HUH?
IT COULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE FACT
THAT MAYBE I'M A GOOD LISTENER
AND I PUT ON A GREAT SLIDE SHOW.
ROSS, I AM TELLING YOU
SHE IS USING YOU
TO GET BACK AT ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
GOOD-BYE.
WHOA.
UH, THAT WAS YOUR SISTER,
ACTUALLY.
SHE... SHE THINKS
YOU'RE JUST USING ME.
SO?
HEY.
SO, I JUST CAME
FROM THE COMPANY
URSULA WORKS FOR.
OH, NO, NOT YOU, TOO?
NO, I JUST WENT TO PICK UP
PHOEBE BUFFAY'S CHECKS.
THERE WERE A LOT OF THEM.
NICE.
MM-HMM.
AND I WON'T HAVE TO GO
BACK THERE ANYMORE
BECAUSE I GAVE THEM
MY "CORRECT ADDRESS."
THAT'S GREAT, BUT ISN'T
IT GOING TO BOTHER YOU
THAT PEOPLE STILL THINK
YOU'RE A PORN STAR?
OH, NO, NO.
I KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT.
WELL, GOOD.
YEAH.
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE YOU KNOW ME FROM?
I'LL GIVE YOU A
HINT-- FROM PORN!
OKAY?
YEAH, YOUR PERVERT BOYFRIEND
WATCHED ME IN A PORNO MOVIE!
SEE?
YEAH, YEAH.
HEY.
YOU, UH, YOU MAY HAVE BEEN
RIGHT ABOUT JILL.
OH, I KNEW IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
UM, SHE KISSED ME.
WHAT?!
YOU KISSED?
MAYBE WE SHOULD GIVE
THEM SOME PRIVACY.
SHH!
LOOK, I, UH...
I TRIED NOT TO
KISS HER, OKAY?
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE IT.
I MEAN, IT'S PRETTY EASY
NOT TO KISS SOMEONE.
YOU JUST DON'T KISS THEM.
SEE, LOOK AT US
RIGHT NOW, NOT KISSING.
LET ME FINISH, OKAY?
SHE STARTED KISSING
ME, AND I...
DIDN'T STOP IT.
I GUESS I JUST
WASN'T THINKING.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU WEREN'T THINKING.
I'LL GIVE YOU SOMETHING
TO THINK ABOUT.
HOLD ON. JUST...
BUT THEN I STARTED THINKING
AND I STOPPED THE KISSING.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU
FOR TAKING YOUR TONGUE
OUT OF MY SISTER'S MOUTH
LONG ENOUGH TO TELL ME THAT.
LOOK, I REALIZED
THAT, IF ANYTHING
WERE TO HAPPEN
WITH ME AND JILL
THEN NOTHING COULD
EVER HAPPEN WITH US.
WHAT?
NO, I MEAN...
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW IF ANYTHING
IS EVER GOING
TO HAPPEN WITH US...
AGAIN EVER.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO KNOW
THAT IT NEVER COULD.
SO I STOPPED IT.
AND...
SHE GOT MAD AND
BROKE MY PROJECTOR.
WOW.
I-I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
( sobbing )
OH, MY GOD,
ARE YOU CRYING?
I JUST DON'T SEE WHY THOSE TWO
CAN'T WORK THINGS OUT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M LEAVING.
BECAUSE I'M NOT GONNA
SPEND ONE MORE DAY WITH SOMEONE
WHO'S OUT TO SABOTAGE
MY EVERY MOVE.
THAT'S YOU, RACHEL.
YEAH, I GOT THAT.
AND YOU...
I THROW MYSELF
AT YOU
AND YOU SAY NO?
HOW GAY ARE YOU?
YOU TAKE CARE, JILL.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
BYE-BYE.
BYE.
( sobbing ):
I CAN'T BELIEVE JILL'S GONE.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I OPENED A GATE.